# **Matt Homan**

www.linkedin.com/in/matt-homan

1102 Speight Avenue · Waco, TX 76798

(972) 467-7789 · Matt\_Homan1@baylor.edu

# **CAREER PROFILE**

Cybersecurity-based MIS student who excels at communication and problem solving. Committed worker with an abundance of experience in thinking outside-the-box. Strong leader that is able to deliver results on time. Technologically skilled and able to pick up on new skills quickly and efficiently. A wealth of experience in fast-paced, high-pressure environments.

### **EDUCATION**

Baylor University - Waco, Texas

May 2024

### **Bachelor of Business Administration**

- Major: Management Information Systems
- Dean's Academic Honor List: Fall 2022

# **EXPERIENCE**

Baylor University - Waco, Texas

Nov 2023 - Present

# **Cybersecurity Research Assistant**

- Overseeing facility and systems at Central Texas Cyber Range in Baylor Research Innovation Collaborative
- · Managing VMWare vSphere server used by students and faculty to simulate cybersecurity environments

# Researching application of core cybersecurity concepts into Industrial Control Systems

Baylor University - Waco, Texas

Aug 2022 - Nov 2023

# **Cybersecurity Research Assistant**

- Managing a private cloud testing environment that is used for virtualization of real-world cybersecurity applications and systems
- Developing strategy and technology for automation for virtualized hardware and software deployment on a VMWare vSphere server cluster using Ansible and Terraform
- · Researching application of core cybersecurity concepts into Industrial Control Systems

# Royse City ISD - Royse City, Texas

May 2022 - Aug 2022

#### **Technology Specialist Intern**

- Engineered python script that automated address locating for school district, saving several days' worth of work
- Created efficient inventory system for parts and devices
- Assisted teachers and administrators in quickly diagnosing and fixing their various computer hardware and software issues

# **ADDITIONAL**

- Computer Skills: VMWare vSphere, Linux, Windows Server/Active Directory, ProxMox, C++, Java, MySQL, Apache2, nginx
- Organizations: Captain of the Baylor Collegiate Cyber Defense Competition team, Founder and

President of Baylor Cybersecurity Club, Computing for Compassion member

• Awards: WACODE 2022 Hackathon Novice bracket winner